Guide to the Professional Staff Congress/City University of New York Records WAG.009
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series III: Records of the Professional Staff Congress, 1926-2016; 108492
  - Subseries III:C: General Files, 1969-2016; 108580
    - Legislative Conference Election Campaign Audit, 1972; 108852 (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - Lehman College Chapter, 1973-1976; 108851 (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - Lehman College Chapter, 1977-1982; 108850 (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - Lehman College Chapter, 1983-1988, 1993-1997; 108849 (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - Librarians, 1974-1982, 1988; 108848 (Box 62, Folder 5)
    - Loyalty Oaths, 1974; 108847 (Box 62, Folder 6)
    - Making It Through College, 1984; 108846 (Box 62, Folder 7)
    - Manhattan Educational Opportunity Center, 1977-1983; 108845 (Box 62, Folder 8)
    - Maternity Issues, undated, 1970-1980; 108844 (Box 62, Folder 9)
    - Mathematics Programs, CUNY (Proposal), undated; 108843 (Box 62, Folder 10)
    - McCarthy Era Dismissals, 1976-1982; 108842 (Box 62, Folder 11)
    - Medgar Evers College Chapter, 1972-1985, 1994; 108841 (Box 62, Folder 12)
    - Melani Case, 1973-1977, 1987; 108840 (Box 62, Folder 13)
    - Membership Committee, 1972-1974; 108839 (Box 62, Folder 14)
    - Membership Figures, 1973-1974, 1979-1981; 108838 (Box 62, Folder 15)
    - Memos: General, 1980-1982; 108837 (Box 62, Folder 16)
    - Memos: General, 1983-1985; 108836 (Box 62, Folder 17)
    - Memos: General, 1988-1992; 108835 (Box 62, Folder 18)
    - Merger, 1972; 108834 (Box 62, Folder 19)
    - Minimum Wage, 1979; 108833 (Box 62, Folder 20)
    - Moynihan, Daniel Patrick: On George Meany, 1977; 108832 (Box 62, Folder 21)
    - Multiple Positions, 1974-1980; 108831 (Box 62, Folder 22)
    - Municipal Labor Committee, 1978, 1981-1989; 108830 (Box 62, Folder 23)
    - Municipal Labor Committee, 1990-1994; 108829 (Box 62, Folder 24)
    - National Center for Educational Statistics, 1975-1981; 108828 (Box 62, Folder 25)
    - National Coalition against Censorship, 1981; 108827 (Box 62, Folder 26)
    - National Council of Senior Citizens, 1982-1988; 108826 (Box 62, Folder 27)
    - National Education Association, 1972-1979; 108825 (Box 62, Folder 28)
    - National Pension Service, 1979-1981; 108824 (Box 62, Folder 29)
    - New Caucus, 1995-1996; 108823 (Box 62, Folder 30)
    - New York City Central Labor Council: Election, 1986; 108822 (Box 62, Folder 31)
    - New York City Community College (NYCCC) Chapter, undated, 1972-1973; 108821 (Box 62, Folder 32)
    - NYCCC Chapter, 1974-1975; 108820 (Box 62, Folder 33)
    - NYCCC Chapter, 1976; 108819 (Box 62, Folder 34)
    - NYCCC Chapter, undated; 108818 (Box 62, Folder 35)
    - New York City Technical College Chapter, 1980-1997; 108817 (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - New York State Education Department: Board of Regents, 1979-1980; 108816 (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - New York State Education Department: Board of Regents, 1981; 108815 (Box 63, Folder 3)
    - New York State Supreme Court: Decision on Academic Judgement, undated; 108814 (Box 63, Folder 4)
    - New York State United Teachers (NYSUT), undated, 1972; 108813 (Box 63, Folder 5)
    - NYSUT (I), 1973; 108812 (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - NYSUT (II), 1973; 108811 (Box 63, Folder 7)
    - NYSUT, 1974; 108810 (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - NYSUT (I), 1975; 108809 (Box 63, Folder 9)
    - NYSUT (II), 1975; 108808 (Box 63, Folder 10)
    - NYSUT, 1976; 108807 (Box 63, Folder 11)
    - NYSUT, 1977; 108806 (Box 63, Folder 12)
    - NYSUT, 1978; 108805 (Box 63, Folder 13)
    - NYSUT (I), 1979; 108804 (Box 63, Folder 14)
    - NYSUT (II), 1979; 108803 (Box 63, Folder 15)
    - NYSUT, 1980; 108802 (Box 63, Folder 16)
    - NYSUT, 1981, 1987; 108801 (Box 63, Folder 17)
    - NYSUT: Board of Directors Meetings, 1974; 108800 (Box 63, Folder 18)
    - NYSUT: Board of Directors Meetings (I), 1975; 108799 (Box 63, Folder 19)
    - NYSUT: Board of Directors Meetings (II), 1975; 108798 (Box 63, Folder 20)
    - NYSUT: Board of Directors Meetings (III), 1975; 108797 (Box 63, Folder 21)
    - NYSUT: Board of Directors Meetings, 1976; 108796 (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - NYSUT: Board of Directors Meetings, 1977; 108795 (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - NYSUT: Board of Directors Meetings, 1978; 108794 (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - NYSUT: Board of Directors Meetings, 1979-1981, 1989; 108793 (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - NYSUT: Election, 1978; 108792 (Box 64, Folder 5)
    - NYSUT: Legislative, undated, 1973-1976; 108791 (Box 64, Folder 6)
    - NYSUT: Legislative, 1981-1985; 108790 (Box 64, Folder 7)
    - NYSUT: Legislative, 1986-1990; 108789 (Box 64, Folder 8)
    - NYSUT: Legislative, 1991; 108788 (Box 64, Folder 9)
    - NYSUT: PSC Relations, 1974; 108787 (Box 64, Folder 10)
    - NYSUT: Training Courses, undated; 108786 (Box 64, Folder 11)
    - NYSUT: TURN Caucus, 1985; 108785 (Box 64, Folder 12)
    - New York Trade Union Women: Conference, 1973-1974; 108784 (Box 64, Folder 13)
    - New York University: Unions, 1985-1987; 108783 (Box 64, Folder 14)
    - Newt Davidson Collective, 1973-1974; 108782 (Box 64, Folder 15)
    - Nicaragua: Albert Shanker's Views, 1985-1986; 108781 (Box 64, Folder 16)
    - Non-Academic Employment, 1978; 108780 (Box 64, Folder 17)
    - O'Dwyer, Paul, 1973; 108779 (Box 64, Folder 18)
    - Office Management, 1972-1973; 108778 (Box 64, Folder 19)
    - Office Professional Employees International Union (OPEIU) Local 153, 1977, 1981; 108777 (Box 64, Folder 20)
    - Office Space, 1982; 108776 (Box 64, Folder 21)
    - Officers List (PSC), 1984; 108775 (Box 64, Folder 22)
    - Open Admissions, undated, 1972; 108774 (Box 64, Folder 23)
    - Open Admissions, 1973; 108773 (Box 64, Folder 24)
    - Open Admissions (I), 1974; 108772 (Box 64, Folder 25)
    - Open Admissions (II), 1974; 108771 (Box 64, Folder 26)
    - Open Admissions, 1975-1976; 108770 (Box 64, Folder 27)
    - Open Admissions, 1977-1979; 108769 (Box 64, Folder 28)
    - Open Admissions, 1980-1991; 108768 (Box 64, Folder 29)
    - Open Admissions: Tuition, 1972-1979; 108767 (Box 64, Folder 30)
    - Opportunity U., 1978; 108766 (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - Opportunity U. (NY Times), 1979; 108765 (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - Panken, Irving: Correspondence, 1976-1978; 108764 (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - Panken, Irving: Correspondence, 1979; 108763 (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - Part-Time Faculty, 1979, 1987, 1994; 108762 (Box 65, Folder 5)
    - Part-Time Students, 1978; 108761 (Box 65, Folder 6)
    - Pauk v. PSC, 1973-1974; 108760 (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - Pell Grants, 1982; 108759 (Box 65, Folder 8)
    - Personnel and Budget Committees (PERB Case), 1974; 108758 (Box 65, Folder 9)
    - Policy Advisory Council, 1973-1976; 108757 (Box 65, Folder 10)
    - Polishook, Irwin: Biographical Information, 1985; 108756 (Box 65, Folder 11)
    - Polishook, Irwin: Correspondence, 1973-1976; 108755 (Box 65, Folder 12)
    - Polishook, Irwin: Correspondence, 1977; 108754 (Box 65, Folder 13)
    - Polishook, Irwin: Correspondence, 1978; 108753 (Box 65, Folder 14)
    - Polishook, Irwin: Correspondence, 1979, 1986; 108752 (Box 65, Folder 15)
    - Polishook, Irwin: Writings and Statements, 1991-1993, 1996; 108751 (Box 65, Folder 16)
    - Political Contributions, undated; 108750 (Box 65, Folder 17)
    - Pre-Retirement Conference, 1979-1983; 108749 (Box 65, Folder 18)
    - Pre-Retirement Conference, 1984-1986; 108748 (Box 65, Folder 19)
    - Press Releases, 1972-1973; 108747 (Box 65, Folder 20)
    - Press Releases, 1974; 108746 (Box 65, Folder 21)
    - Press Releases, 1975; 108745 (Box 65, Folder 22)
    - Press Releases, 1976; 108744 (Box 65, Folder 23)
    - PSC History, undated, 1974, 1981-1982; 108743 (Box 65, Folder 24)
    - PSC Hotline, 1976; 108742 (Box 65, Folder 25)
    - PSC Hotline, 1977-1978; 108741 (Box 65, Folder 26)
    - PSC Hotline, 1980-1981; 108740 (Box 65, Folder 27)
    - PSC Hotline, 1984-1987; 108739 (Box 65, Folder 28)
    - PSC Hotline, 1988-1990; 108738 (Box 65, Folder 29)
    - PSC Hotline, 1991-1994; 108737 (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - PSC Hotline, 1995-1997; 108736 (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - Progressive Caucus, 1973, 1978; 108735 (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - Proposition 13 (California), 1979; 108734 (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - Proshansky, Harold, 1989; 108733 (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - Public Employee Legislative Conference, undated, 1976, 1979; 108732 (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - Public Employees and Collective Bargaining, 1972-1979; 108731 (Box 66, Folder 7)
    - Public Relations, 1973; 108730 (Box 66, Folder 8)
    - Queens College: Black Issues, 1980; 108729 (Box 66, Folder 9)
    - Queens College Chapter, 1972; 108728 (Box 66, Folder 10)
    - Queens College Chapter (I), 1973; 108727 (Box 66, Folder 11)
    - Queens College Chapter (II), 1973; 108726 (Box 66, Folder 12)
    - Queens College Chapter, 1974; 108725 (Box 66, Folder 13)
    - Queens College Chapter, 1975; 108724 (Box 66, Folder 14)
    - Queens College Chapter, 1976; 108723 (Box 66, Folder 15)
    - Queens College Chapter, 1977-1981; 108722 (Box 66, Folder 16)
    - Queens College Chapter, 1983-1997; 108721 (Box 66, Folder 17)
    - Queensborough Community College: Black Faculty, 1975; 108720 (Box 66, Folder 18)
    - Queensborough Community College Chapter, undated, 1972-1973; 108719 (Box 66, Folder 19)
    - Queensborough Community College Chapter, 1974-1978; 108718 (Box 66, Folder 20)
    - Queensborough Community College Chapter, 1982-1997; 108717 (Box 66, Folder 21)
    - Race and Education, 1979; 108716 (Box 66, Folder 22)
    - Rank and File Caucus, 1974; 108715 (Box 66, Folder 23)
    - Referenda, undated; 108714 (Box 66, Folder 24)
    - Regents: Reports, etc., 1972-1977; 108713 (Box 66, Folder 25)
    - Registrar/Admissions (RA) Professionals Chapter, 1980-1981, 1995-1997; 108712 (Box 66, Folder 26)
    - Remediation, 1979; 108711 (Box 66, Folder 27)
    - Research Awards, undated, 1972-1976; 108710 (Box 66, Folder 28)
    - Research Foundation Chapter, undated, 1973; 108709 (Box 66, Folder 29)
    - Research Foundation Chapter, 1974-1975; 108708 (Box 66, Folder 30)
    - Research Foundation Chapter, 1976; 108707 (Box 66, Folder 31)
    - Research Foundation Chapter, 1977-1979; 108706 (Box 66, Folder 32)
    - Research Foundation Chapter, 1980-1983; 108705 (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - Research Foundation Chapter, 1984-1991; 108704 (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - Research Foundation Chapter, 1994-1995; 108703 (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - Residency Rules, 1974-1978; 108702 (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - Restructuring, 1975-1976; 108701 (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - Retirees Chapter, undated, 1974-1976; 108700 (Box 67, Folder 6)
    - Retirees Chapter, 1977-1978; 108699 (Box 67, Folder 7)
    - Retirees Chapter, 1979-1981; 108698 (Box 67, Folder 8)
    - Retirees Chapter, 1982-1983; 108697 (Box 67, Folder 9)
    - Retirees Chapter, 1984; 108696 (Box 67, Folder 10)
    - Retirees Chapter, 1985-1986; 108695 (Box 67, Folder 11)
    - Retirees Chapter, 1987-1989; 108694 (Box 67, Folder 12)
    - Retirees Chapter, 1990-1992; 108693 (Box 67, Folder 13)
    - Retirees Chapter, 1993-1997; 108692 (Box 67, Folder 14)
    - Retirees Chapter (Florida), 1982-1986; 108691 (Box 67, Folder 15)
    - Retirees Chapter: Weinberg Retirement, 1983; 108690 (Box 67, Folder 16)
    - Retrenchment, undated, 1974-1977; 108689 (Box 67, Folder 17)
    - Retrenchment, 1982; 108688 (Box 67, Folder 18)
    - Retrenchment, 1983; 108687 (Box 67, Folder 19)
    - Retrenchment, 1992-1993; 108686 (Box 67, Folder 20)
    - Retrenchment: Temple University, 1981; 108685 (Box 67, Folder 21)
    - Reverse Discrimination, undated, 1972-1977; 108684 (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - Rodriguez-Abad, Louis, undated, 1973-1978; 108683 (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - Rustin, Bayard, 1985-1987; 108682 (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - Sabbaticals, 1975-1981; 108681 (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - Salaries, 1972-1979; 108680 (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - Salaries: City College School of Engineering, undated; 108679 (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - Scholarly Incentive Award, 1985-1986; 108678 (Box 68, Folder 7)
    - Scholars in Transition, 1985; 108677 (Box 68, Folder 8)
    - Scholarly Journal (PSC), 1978; 108676 (Box 68, Folder 9)
    - School Law Newsletter, 1974-1975; 108675 (Box 68, Folder 10)
    - Search for Education, Elevation, and Knowledge Program (SEEK), 1972-1976; 108674 (Box 68, Folder 11)
    - SEEK, 1977; 108673 (Box 68, Folder 12)
    - SEEK, 1978-1986; 108672 (Box 68, Folder 13)
    - SEEK, 1987-1989; 108671 (Box 68, Folder 14)
    - SEEK: Chancellor's Task Force on Performance and Achievement, 1979-1980; 108670 (Box 68, Folder 15)
    - Senate Tax Bill: Cap on Defined Benefit Plan, 1986; 108669 (Box 68, Folder 16)
    - Seniority, 1976-1977; 108668 (Box 68, Folder 17)
    - Sex Discrimination, undated, 1972-1973; 108667 (Box 68, Folder 18)
    - Sex Discrimination, 1974-1975; 108666 (Box 68, Folder 19)
    - Sex Discrimination, 1976-1979; 108665 (Box 68, Folder 20)
    - Sex Discrimination: Dushane Fund, undated, 1972-1976; 108664 (Box 68, Folder 21)
    - Sex Discrimination: Hunter College, 1975-1978; 108663 (Box 68, Folder 22)
    - Sex Discrimination: Title IX, undated, 1972-1982; 108662 (Box 68, Folder 23)
    - Sex Discrimination: Title IX - Women and Sports, 1974-1977; 108661 (Box 68, Folder 24)
    - Sick Leave, 1976; 108660 (Box 68, Folder 25)
    - Sloan Commission on Government and Higher Education, 1979; 108659 (Box 68, Folder 26)
    - Social Security, undated, 1983-1986; 108658 (Box 68, Folder 27)
    - Solidarity Day, 1981; 108657 (Box 68, Folder 28)
    - Staff (PSC), 1983-1984; 108656 (Box 68, Folder 29)
    - Standing Committees, 1973-1976; 108655 (Box 68, Folder 30)
    - Starling, Marion, 1982; 108654 (Box 68, Folder 31)
    - State Aid to Higher Education, 1978-1982; 108653 (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - State University of New York (SUNY): Budget, 1978-1980; 108652 (Box 69, Folder 2)
    - SUNY: Purchase, 1980; 108651 (Box 69, Folder 3)
    - Staten Island Community College, 1972-1973; 108650 (Box 69, Folder 4)
    - Staten Island Community College, 1974-1975; 108649 (Box 69, Folder 5)
    - Staten Island Community College, 1976-1978; 108648 (Box 69, Folder 6)
    - Student Activism, undated; 108647 (Box 69, Folder 7)
    - Student Activity Fees, 1981; 108646 (Box 69, Folder 8)
    - Student Attrition, undated; 108645 (Box 69, Folder 9)
    - Student-Faculty Ratios, 1979; 108644 (Box 69, Folder 10)
    - Student Loans, 1978-1981; 108643 (Box 69, Folder 11)
    - Student Performance, By State, 1987; 108642 (Box 69, Folder 12)
    - Student Rights (Student Senate of CUNY), undated, 1972-1973; 108641 (Box 69, Folder 13)
    - Student Rights (Student Senate of CUNY), 1974-1976; 108640 (Box 69, Folder 14)
    - Student Senate of CUNY, 1980-1981; 108639 (Box 69, Folder 15)
    - Student Senate of CUNY Newspaper, 1974-1976; 108638 (Box 69, Folder 16)
    - Task Force on Higher Education: Draft Report, 1975; 108637 (Box 69, Folder 17)
    - Tax: New York State, 1983; 108636 (Box 69, Folder 18)
    - Tax Issues, 1973-1980; 108635 (Box 69, Folder 19)
    - Tax Limitation Movement, 1978-1979; 108634 (Box 69, Folder 20)
    - Taylor Law, 1973-1978; 108633 (Box 69, Folder 21)
    - Teachers Retirement Board, undated, 1980-1983; 108632 (Box 69, Folder 22)
    - Teachers Retirement System, 1991-1992; 108631 (Box 69, Folder 23)
    - Teaching Assistants, 1980; 108630 (Box 69, Folder 24)
    - Tenure, undated, 1973; 108629 (Box 69, Folder 25)
    - Tenure, 1974-1976; 108628 (Box 69, Folder 26)
    - Tenure, 1978-1981; 108627 (Box 69, Folder 27)
    - Tenure Quotas, undated, 1972-1973; 108626 (Box 69, Folder 28)
    - Tenure Quotas, 1974-1975; 108625 (Box 69, Folder 29)
    - Testimony, 1975-1977; 108624 (Box 69, Folder 30)
    - Testing, 1973-1974; 108623 (Box 69, Folder 31)
    - Testing: Truth in Testing Bill, 1978-1980; 108622 (Box 69, Folder 32)
    - Tuition, 1979; 108621 (Box 69, Folder 33)
    - Tuition Remission Policies, 1977-1979; 108620 (Box 69, Folder 34)
    - Tuition Tax Credits, 1978-1979; 108619 (Box 69, Folder 35)
    - Unemployment Cases, 1975-1981; 108618 (Box 70, Folder 1)
    - Unemployment Insurance, undated, 1972-1983; 108617 (Box 70, Folder 2)
    - Union Caucus, undated, 1973-1988; 108616 (Box 70, Folder 3)
    - UFCT Arbitration Case, 1973; 108615 (Box 70, Folder 4)
    - UFCT History, 1972; 108614 (Box 70, Folder 5)
    - UFCT: Job Security, 1969; 108613 (Box 70, Folder 5a)
    - UFT "Raids" AFSCME, 1973-1974; 108612 (Box 70, Folder 6)
    - United Jewish Appeal Federation, 1986; 108611 (Box 70, Folder 7)
    - United States Department of Education (Pro & Con), 1977-1981; 108610 (Box 70, Folder 8)
    - United University Professions (UUP), 1985-1987; 108609 (Box 70, Folder 9)
    - Unity Caucus, undated; 108608 (Box 70, Folder 10)
    - Unity Caucus, 1989-1990; 108607 (Box 70, Folder 11)
    - Urban Center Chapter, 1972; 108606 (Box 70, Folder 12)
    - Vladeck, Judith: Reception, 1987; 108605 (Box 70, Folder 13)
    - Vladeck, Stephen, 1973, 1979; 108604 (Box 70, Folder 14)
    - Wagner Labor Archives, NYU, 1981; 108603 (Box 70, Folder 15)
    - Weiss, Clarissa (Gilbert): Correspondence, undated, 1978-1981; 108602 (Box 70, Folder 16)
    - Weiss, Clarissa (Gilbert): Correspondence, 1984-1987; 108601 (Box 70, Folder 17)
    - Weiss, Clarissa (Gilbert): Correspondence, 1990-1991; 108600 (Box 70, Folder 18)
    - Weiss, Clarissa (Gilbert): Correspondence, 1992; 108599 (Box 70, Folder 19)
    - Weiss, Clarissa (Gilbert): Invitations, 1984-1997; 108598 (Box 70, Folder 20)
    - Wessel Commission, 1976-1977; 108597 (Box 70, Folder 21)
    - White House Conference on Aging, 1978-1981; 108596 (Box 70, Folder 22)
    - Why Go To College?, 1980; 108595 (Box 70, Folder 23)
    - Wilson, Governor Malcolm, 1973-1974; 108594 (Box 70, Folder 24)
    - Women in Higher Education, undated, 1972-1980; 108593 (Box 70, Folder 25)
    - Women's Education Equity Act, undated, 1975-1977; 108592 (Box 70, Folder 26)
    - Women's Issues, undated, 1973-1981; 108591 (Box 70, Folder 27)
    - Women's Studies, 1972, 1979; 108590 (Box 70, Folder 28)
    - Women's Studies: City College, 1972-1973; 108589 (Box 70, Folder 29)
    - Workers Compensation, 1982-1989; 108588 (Box 70, Folder 30)
    - Wordload, 1971-1975, 1985; 108587 (Box 70, Folder 31)
    - Workplace Privacy, 1979-1980; 108586 (Box 70, Folder 32)
    - Yellowitz, Irwin, 1984-1987; 108585 (Box 70, Folder 33)
    - Yeshiva Decision, 1979-1981; 108584 (Box 70, Folder 34)
    - York College Chapter, 1973-1977, 1980-1987; 108583 (Box 70, Folder 35)
    - Zeller, Belle: Scholarship Fund, 1982-1985; 108582 (Box 70, Folder 36)
    - Ziskind, Robert, 1983-1986; 108581 (Box 70, Folder 37)
  - Subseries III:D: Benefits-Related Files, 1972-1995; 108493
    - Benefits: General, 1973-1991; 108579 (Box 71, Folder 1)
    - Benefits: "Cafeteria Plan", 1984-1986; 108578 (Box 71, Folder 2)
    - Benefits: Correspondence (C. Weiss), 1988; 108577 (Box 71, Folder 3)
    - Benefits: Correspondence (C. Weiss) I, 1989; 108576 (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - Benefits: Correspondence (C. Weiss) II, 1989; 108575 (Box 71, Folder 5)
    - Benefits: Disability, undated; 108574 (Box 71, Folder 6)
    - Benefits: Leave of Absence - Travia Leave, 1974-1977, 1982; 108573 (Box 71, Folder 7)
    - Benefits: "Manhart" Refunds, undated; 108572 (Box 71, Folder 8)
    - Benefits: Medical, 1972-1982; 108571 (Box 71, Folder 9)
    - Benefits: Medical, 1983-1989; 108570 (Box 71, Folder 10)
    - Benefits: Medical (TIAA), 1974-1976, 1980-1982; 108569 (Box 71, Folder 11)
    - Benefits: Members' Problems, 1975-1979; 108568 (Box 71, Folder 12)
    - Benefits: NYSUT, 1977-1982; 108567 (Box 71, Folder 13)
    - Benefits: Pension, undated, 1972-1983; 108566 (Box 71, Folder 14)
    - Benefits: Pension, 1986-1995; 108565 (Box 71, Folder 15)
    - Benefits: Pension - Bindler v. Goldin, 1978-1980; 108564 (Box 71, Folder 16)
    - Benefits: Pension - Sex Discrimination, 1979-1983; 108563 (Box 71, Folder 17)
    - Benefits: Pension - State Commission on Pensions, undated, 1987; 108562 (Box 71, Folder 18)
    - Benefits: Pension Transfers (ERS-TRS) - General, undated, 1986-1987; 108561 (Box 71, Folder 19)
    - Benefits: Pension Transfers (ERS-TRS) - Bill, undated, 1976-1987; 108560 (Box 71, Folder 20)
    - Benefits: Pension Transfers (ERS-TRS) - Cases, etc., 1973-1979; 108559 (Box 71, Folder 21)
    - Benefits: Pension/Welfare Benefits Memos, 1973-1974; 108558 (Box 71, Folder 22)
    - Benefits: Pension/Welfare Benefits Memos, 1975; 108557 (Box 71, Folder 23)
    - Benefits: Pension/Welfare Benefits Memos, 1976-1982; 108556 (Box 71, Folder 24)
    - Benefits: Research Foundation, 1972-1982; 108555 (Box 71, Folder 25)
    - Benefits: Tax-Deferred Annuities, 1980-1986; 108554 (Box 71, Folder 26)
    - Blue Cross/Blue Shield, 1983, 1986; 108553 (Box 72, Folder 1)
    - Employment Retirement Income Security Act (ERISA), 1974-1981; 108552 (Box 72, Folder 2)
    - Health Plan: Correspondence, 1977-1980; 108551 (Box 72, Folder 3)
    - Health Plan: Correspondence, 1984-1990; 108550 (Box 72, Folder 4)
    - Health Plan Re-Opener, 1980; 108549 (Box 72, Folder 5)
    - Health Plan Transfers, undated, 1978-1981; 108548 (Box 72, Folder 6)
    - Pension Committee: General, 1973-1978, 1980-1986; 108547 (Box 72, Folder 7)
    - Pension Committee: Meetings, 1977-1978; 108546 (Box 72, Folder 8)
    - Pension Committee: Meetings, 1979; 108545 (Box 72, Folder 9)
    - Pension Committee: Meetings, 1980; 108544 (Box 72, Folder 10)
    - Pension Committee: Meetings, 1981; 108543 (Box 72, Folder 11)
    - Pension Committee: Meetings, 1982, 1985-1987; 108542 (Box 72, Folder 12)
    - Pension Committee: Minutes, 1973-1979; 108541 (Box 72, Folder 13)
    - Pension Committee: Minutes, 1982-1986; 108540 (Box 72, Folder 14)
    - Pension Handbook, 1983; 108539 (Box 72, Folder 15)
    - Pension Supplementation Bill, 1987; 108538 (Box 72, Folder 16)
    - Pension Watchdog Committee, undated; 108537 (Box 72, Folder 17)
    - Retirement, 1978; 108536 (Box 72, Folder 18)
    - Retirement: Correspondence, 1972-1982; 108535 (Box 72, Folder 19)
    - Retirement: Correspondence, 1991-1994; 108534 (Box 72, Folder 20)
    - Retirement: Early Retirement, 1981-1992; 108533 (Box 72, Folder 21)
    - Retirement: Horowitz Case, 1982-1983; 108532 (Box 72, Folder 22)
    - Retirement: Horowitz Case, 1985; 108531 (Box 72, Folder 23)
    - Retirement Incentive Act, 1990, 1992; 108530 (Box 73, Folder 1)
    - Retirement: Mandatory, 1972-1990; 108529 (Box 73, Folder 2)
    - Retirement Plan Options, 1984; 108528 (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - Retirement Planning: "Ready or Not" Programs, undated, 1980; 108527 (Box 73, Folder 4)
    - Retirement Planning: "Ready or Not" Programs, 1981-1984; 108526 (Box 73, Folder 5)
    - Retirement Planning: "Ready or Not" Programs, 1985-1989; 108525 (Box 73, Folder 6)
    - Retirement: Second Careers, 1983-1984; 108524 (Box 73, Folder 7)
    - Retirement: Sullivan Study, 1980; 108523 (Box 73, Folder 8)
    - Tax Prep Transfer, 1982; 108522 (Box 73, Folder 9)
    - Tax Proposals: Federal, 1985; 108521 (Box 73, Folder 10)
    - Teachers' Insurance & Annuity Association (TIAA), 1984-1994; 108520 (Box 73, Folder 11)
    - TIAA: Bindler Case, 1980-1981; 108519 (Box 73, Folder 12)
    - TIAA: Disability, 1981-1984; 108518 (Box 73, Folder 13)
    - Unemployment Benefits, 1976; 108517 (Box 73, Folder 14)
    - Weinberg, Beryl: Correspondence, 1975-1978; 108516 (Box 73, Folder 15)
    - Weinberg, Beryl: Correspondence, 1979; 108515 (Box 73, Folder 16)
    - Weinberg, Beryl: Correspondence, 1980; 108514 (Box 73, Folder 17)
    - Weinberg, Beryl: Correspondence, 1981; 108513 (Box 73, Folder 18)
    - Weinberg, Beryl: Correspondence, 1982-1984; 108512 (Box 73, Folder 19)
    - Welfare Committee (Ad Hoc), 1978; 108511 (Box 73, Folder 20)
    - Welfare Fund, undated, 1972-1983; 108510 (Box 73, Folder 21)